자막제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/24)
'24' Season 7
Epi 08. 03:00 P.M. - 04:00 P.M.
'24' 지난 줄거리
Previously on 24
FBI에서 다음 공격 대상을
찾았다고 믿고 있습니다
The FBI believes they've detected
where the next attack will take place.
오하이오주 키드론
외곽의 화학 공장입니다
A chemical plant
just outside of Kidron, Ohio.
예측 시간이 어떻게 되지?
What's our time frame?
탱크가 15분 안에
터질 수 있습니다
The tank could rupture
in less than 15 minutes.
지금 이걸 막을 유일한 방법은
두바쿠와 CIP 장치를 찾는 겁니다
Right now our best chance to stop this
is by finding Dubaku and the CIP device.
400PSI까지 올라갔습니다
400 PSI.
탱크가 터질 때까지
얼마나 남았지?
How long before the tank ruptures?
- 7분입니다
- 문제가 생겼습니다
- Seven minutes.
- We've got a problem.
알메이다와 바우어를
죽인 줄 알았는데
I thought you killed Almeida and Bauer.
- 젠장! 우릴 어떻게 찾았냐고?
- 몰라요!
- Damn it! How did they find us?
- I don't know!
건물 안으로 들어왔습니다
They're in the building.
CIP 모듈을 분리하고
철수를 시작해
Disengage the CIP module.
Begin the offload.
잭, CIP 장치는 파괴됐어요
Jack, I've got the CIP device!
It's been destroyed.
마토보 내외는 안전해요
밴으로 모셔 갈게요
The Matobos are safe.
I'm taking them to the van.
알았어요
Copy that.
자네는 빌과 두바쿠를 찾아봐
You and Bill do a sweep.
See if you can find Dubaku.
인구 수백만의 도시에서
한 사람을 찾기엔 역부족이니
We are not equipped to look for
one man in a city of millions.
- 추가 지원이 필요해요
- 정부 말이야?
- We need additional resources.
- The government?
믿으면 안 돼요, 아무도 못 믿으니까
단독으로 진행하는 거잖아요
They can't be trusted.
We can't trust anybody.
That's why we're working on the outside.
테일러 대통령은
믿을 수 있어요
President Taylor can be trusted.
대통령님, 드릴 말씀이 있습니다
Madam President,
you need to listen to me.
저흴 구출해준 사람들이
CIP 장치를 파괴해서
The people who rescued us,
they have acquired the CIP device.
It's being destroyed, and your country's
no longer under immediate threat.
귀국에 대한 즉각적인
위협은 사라졌습니다
그 사람들이 누굽니까?
Who are these people?
대통령님만 따로 뵙고
직접 말씀드리겠습니다
I'll tell you everything in person,
but I must speak to you alone.
헨리를 연결해 줘요
Please get Henry on the phone.
부군께 연락이 안 됩니다
Henry's unreachable.
게지 요원한테 연락하려는데
응답이 없습니다
I've been trying to reach Agent Gedge,
and he hasn't picked up.
사만다 로스의 아파트 밖에서
부군을 기다리고 있다고 했어요
He said he was outside Samantha Roth's
apartment waiting for the First Gentleman.
남편이 실종됐다는 건가요?
You're telling me my husband's
gone missing?
게지는 죽었어요
Gedge is dead.
- 무슨 일이야?
- 뭔가 틀어졌는지
- What happened?
- Something went wrong.
테일러가 어떻게 게지를 죽였어요
Taylor killed Gedge,
I don't know how.
죽이지 말고 나한테 데려와
Don't kill him.
Bring him to me.
이 이야기는 오후 3시에서
4시 사이에 일어난 일입니다
The following takes place
between 3:00 p.m. and 4:00 p.m.
FOX 방영일 : 2009년 2월 9일
ORIGINAL AIR DATE ON FOX
2009/02/09
동영상 정보
HDTV-LOL / 349MB
SYNC BASED ON
미행은 없는지 확인했어요?
You're certain you weren't followed?
네, 트렁크에서
꺼내는 것 좀 도와줘요
Yes. Come on.
Help me get him inside.
워싱턴 상공과 오하이오주
키드론에서 벌어진 비극이
We can confirm at this point
the tragedies that unfolded in the skies
over Washington and in Kidron, Ohio,
실로 테러 행위였음이
밝혀졌습니다
were indeed acts of terrorism.
그러나 더는 위협이 존재하지 않는다고
국민 여러분께 확실히 말씀드립니다
But I am here to assure you
that those responsible are
no longer a threat to this country.
상갈라 학살에 대한 개입을 막으려는
시도는 실패로 돌아갔으며
Their attempts to stop us from intervening
in the Sangalan genocide have failed.
우리는 테러에
굴복하지 않을 것입니다
We will not give in to terrorists.
방금 전, 상갈라 국민의 해방을 위한
군사 작전 개시를 지시했습니다
A short time ago, I gave the order
for our troops to begin operations
that will liberate
the people of Sangala.
주마 정권은
곧 붕괴할 것이라 확신하며
We are confident that
the Juma regime will collapse swiftly,
울레 마토보 수상의 지도하에
민주주의가 재건될 것입니다
and that democracy will be restored under
the leadership of Prime Minister Ule Matobo.
- 너희 둘, 따라와
- 네
- You, you, come.
- Yes, sir.
수고했네, 보슬러 요원
Well done, Agent Vossler.
4시에 교대가 있어서
가봐야 해요
I've got to go now.
I've got a shift that starts at 4:00.
그럼 가게, 돈은
기존 계좌로 송금하지
Then go.
Your money will be wired
to the usual account.
이 방은 방음이 돼 있어서
도움을 청해 봤자 소용없소
The room is soundproof, Mr. Taylor.
There's no point in screaming
or trying to call for help.
엘리무, 재갈을 풀어
Elimu, remove Mr. Taylor's gag.
이 나쁜 자식
You son of a bitch.
네놈이 내 아들을 죽인 배후군
You're behind my son's death.
당신 아들이
쓸데없는 참견을 했지
He was poking his nose
where it did not belong.
모두가 날 찾고 있을 테니
절대 빠져나갈 수 없을 거다
You'll never get away with this.
You must know that.
Everyone in the city is
going to be looking for me.
하나만 생각하시오, 테일러 씨
You should be concerned with
just one question, Mr. Taylor.
상갈라 침공을 취소할 만큼
대통령이 당신을 사랑하는지
Does your wife love you enough to
call off the invasion of my country?
당신을 생각한다면
그러길 바라야지
For your sake,
I hope the answer is yes.
보안 장치를 작동해
Activate the scrambling device.
법 집행 기관에서 관련자들을 추적해
법의 심판을 받게 할 것입니다
Our law enforcement agencies will
hunt down the people responsible
and bring them to justice.
국민 여러분께 부탁드리건대
오늘 목숨을 잃은 희생자들과 유가족
I ask now that your thoughts and prayers
go to those who lost their lives today,
to their families and loved ones,
and to our troops
그리고 자유의 이름으로 목숨을 내건
우리 군인들을 위해 기도해 주십시오
who are putting their lives on
the line in the name of freedom.
감사합니다
Thank you. Good afternoon.
마토보 수상이 도착했습니다
Matobo's arrived.
믿을 만한 요원들이 수상 일행을
비밀리에 지하 통로로 데려왔습니다
He and the others have been brought in
secretly through the underground entrance
by agents I personally know and trust.
그 일행이 수상을 구출하고
CIP 장치를 되찾았다던데
Matobo told me the people he's bringing
in are responsible for saving his life
and recovering the CIP device.
어떤 사람들이죠?
Who are they?
빌 뷰캐넌은 CTU LA 지부장을
지낼 때 만나신 적이 있고
Bill Buchanan, whom I believe you
met when he headed up CTU L.A.,
르네 워커란 FBI 요원과
잭 바우어입니다
FBI agent named Renee Walker
and Jack Bauer.
바우어는 납치범 중 하나였는데
이해가 안 돼요
Bauer... he was one of Matobo's kidnappers.
Doesn't make sense.
그러게 말입니다
I know.
마토보 수상이 사연을
들어주라 했으니 그렇게 하죠
Matobo asked me to listen
to what they have to say,
and I'm willing to do so.
들여보내요
Send them in.
들어오십시오
The President's ready.
수상님
Ule.
두 분 내외께서 무사하셔서
천만다행입니다
I can't tell you how thankful
we are that you and Alama are safe.
감사합니다, 아내는
뷰캐넌 씨 일행과 회복 중입니다
Thank you. She's with
Mr. Buchanan's people now, recovering.
미국 영토에서
이런 시련을 당하신 건
That you were subjected to
such an ordeal on our soil
개인적으로나
국가적으로 수치입니다
is a source of shame both to me
personally and to my country.
대통령님, 제 주요 관심사는
저 자신이 아니라 상갈라입니다
Madam President, my chief
concern is for Sangala, not myself.
침공 계획은 어떻게 됐습니까?
May I ask what your timetable
is for the invasion?
군에 진행 명령을 내렸습니다
I've issued the order to
our military to proceed.
상갈라 국민에게 큰 힘이 돼주셔서
진심으로 감사드립니다
I thank you with all my heart.
You're doing my people a great service,
이 사람들 역시 귀국에
큰 공헌을 했습니다
much as these people have done
for your country.
죄송하지만
그 말씀은 믿기 힘든데요
Now forgive me, Prime Minister, but
I'm finding that hard to believe.
생각하시는 것과는 다릅니다
I assure you, none of
this is as it seems.
본인들이 설명하기 위해
여기 온 거고요
But they're here to explain themselves.
괜찮으시다면 전 제 측근과
침공 후 계획을 의논하겠습니다
Now, if you'll excuse me,
Madam President,
I must meet with my people
to discuss post-invasion plans.
그러시죠
Of course.
대체 어떻게 된 일인지
당장 설명해 보게
I want an explanation and I want it now.
What the hell is going on?
대통령님, 6주 전
빌 뷰캐넌이 발견한 바로는
Madam President, six weeks ago,
Bill Buchanan discovered that
key members of your government
현 정부 주요 인사들이
주마 장군과 두바쿠 대령과 내통해
were working with General Juma and Colonel Dubaku
in an effort to undermine this nation's foreign policy...
상갈라에 대한 외교 정책을
폄하하려 한다는 것이었습니다
your foreign policy
with regards to Sangala.
그게 얼마나
억지 주장인지 아나?
You realize that that is
an outrageous accusation?
네, 압니다
Yes, ma'am.
불행히도 그건 사실입니다
Unfortunately, it's the truth.
두바쿠를 막으려는 노력이
매번 실패한 것도 그 때문입니다
It explains why during this crisis, every
effort you made to stop Dubaku failed.
빌, 왜 내게 오지 않았나?
Bill, why didn't you come to me?
누굴 믿어야 할지, 제 말씀을
믿어주실지 확신이 없어서
I didn't know who I could trust
or if you'd even believe me.
두바쿠를 추적해 제압할
작은 조직을 결성한 겁니다
So I formed a small group to
locate and neutralize Dubaku.
토니 알메이다, 그리고
마지막엔 잭도 함께했습니다
Tony Almeida and
ultimately, Jack, joined me.
애초에 토니 알메이다가
CIP 장치를 두바쿠에게 넘겼잖나
Tony Almeida was the one who put the CIP
device into Dubaku's hands in the first place.
위장 임무의 일환으로 CIP 장치를
미끼로 써 두바쿠를 추적했습니다
Using the CIP device as bait was
necessary to the undercover operation.
We had to follow it back to Dubaku.
비행기 충돌로
많은 목숨을 잃었네
A lot of people died on those planes,
키드론의 화학 공장에선
더 큰 인명 피해가 있을 뻔했고!
never mind what could have happened
at the chemical plant in Kidron!
대통령님, 말씀 중 죄송하지만
Madam President, if I may,
전 CIP 장치 회수 임무에
배정된 FBI 요원이고
I was part of the FBI task force
assigned to recover the CIP device,
이들이 말하는 것이
사실이라는 걸 보장합니다
and I can personally vouch
for what they're telling you.
희생이 따른 건
분명 비극이지만
The loss of life was tragic,
yes, but in my opinion,
제가 볼 때 이 사람들은
수천 명의 목숨을 구했습니다
everything these men have done
saved the lives of thousands.
내가 자네들의 말을
믿는다고 하면
If I choose to believe everything
you're telling me,
이제 어떻게 할 건가?
where would you go from here?
현 정부 내 배신자 명단을 가진
두바쿠를 찾는 일이 급선무인데
Dubaku is the only person with the names of the people
who betrayed you within your government.
It's imperative that we find him.
비밀리에 진행해야 합니다
We would have to work under the radar.
수사의 기미가 보이면
연루자들이 자취를 감출 겁니다
Any word of an investigation,
people would start running for cover.
FBI나 국토안보부도
믿을 수 없단 말인가?
You're saying we can't even
involve the FBI and Homeland?
네, 그렇습니다
Yes, sir, that's correct.
대통령님, 팀 우즈의
긴급 연락입니다
Madam President, Tim Woods is
on the phone. He says it's urgent.
- 연결하게
- 연결해요
- Put him through.
앉게
Have a seat.
무슨 일인가?
Yes?
대통령님, 방해해서 죄송합니다만
두바쿠에게 전화가 왔습니다
Madam President, I'm sorry to interrupt.
There's a call for you from Ike Dubaku.
음성 확인은 했고
부군에 관한 일이랍니다
Voice I.D. confirms that.
He says it's about your husband.
남편에 관한 일이라고?
My husband?
네, 연결하겠습니다
Yes, ma'am. I'll connect you.
테일러 대통령이다
This is President Taylor.
요점만 말하자면 당신 남편을
데리고 있소, 들어보시지
I'll come straight to the point,
Madam President.
I have your husband.
Let me demonstrate.
얘기해
Say something.
앨리슨
Allison...
헨리, 괜찮아요?
Henry, are you all right?
괜찮아요
I'm fine.
미안해요, 놈들이 날
이용해도 굴복하지 마요
I'm sorry about this.
For god sake, don't let them use me
to influence you in any way.
우리 요구를 말하지
Our demands are as follows:
즉시 상갈라 주변의 병력을
영구히 철수하고
You will have your forces withdrawn
from around my country, Sangala,
immediately and permanently.
스탠즈윅 발전소 동쪽에 있는
내 부하들에게 마토보를 데려오시오
Also, Matobo must be delivered
to my men
who will be stationed at the east
lot of the Stanswick power plant.
4시까지 오지 않거나
If he's not there by 4:00,
발전소를 떠날 때
미행하거나 방해하면
or if anybody attempts to follow or
impede my men when they leave the plant,
남편을 천천히
확실하게 죽여버리겠소
your husband will die
a slow and certain death.
네놈이 감히!
You wouldn't dare!
손가락을 잘라
Cut off his finger.
그만 해!
Stop it!
그만!
요구에 응하지 않으면
한 번에 한 조각씩 보내주지
Meet my demands or I will send him
back to you one piece at a time.
알겠소, 테일러 대통령?
Do you understand, Madam President?
알겠다
Yes, I understand.
남편을 찾으려는 시도는
바로 들통 날 테고
Any attempt to find your husband
will be known to me very quickly,
그 즉시 남편을 죽이겠소
and I will kill him immediately.
부군이 계셨던 장소에 보낸
팀한테 연락이 왔는데
Madam President, I just heard back from
the team I sent to Henry's last-known location.
그곳에서 사만다와 게지 요원의
시신을 발견했답니다
They found Samantha Roth's and
Secret Service Agent Gedge's bodies.
이럴 수가!
Oh, god!
게지가 마취제를
가지고 있었던 점과
Gedge had possession
of a paralytic drug.
다른 현장 증거로 볼 때
부군의 납치를 도운 것 같습니다
That and other evidence on scene suggests
he was complicit in Henry's abduction,
자네 말대로 부패 조직의
존재를 증명하는 것이지
which, of course, confirms
the corruption you just told us about.
대통령님, 시간이 없습니다
대응 방안을 결정해야 합니다
Madam President, time is tight.
We need to decide how to respond.
잠시 침공을 보류한다고 해서
비난할 사람은 없습니다
I don't think anyone would
blame you for holding back,
at least temporarily,
the invasion of Sangala.
비행기 충돌 사상자가
얼마나 되죠?
How many people died
on those planes?
- 얼마예요?
- 300명쯤 됩니다
- How many?
- About 300, ma'am.
전부 내가 상갈라에 대한
방침을 고집한 결과죠
All because I refused to
change course in Sangala.
나 자신이 감수하지 않을 희생을
어떻게 국민에게 요구하겠어요?
How can I ask the American people
to make sacrifices
that I'm not willing to make myself?
물러설 수 없어요
I can't give in. I can't.
대통령님
Madam President...
4시 시한 전까지 아직
부군을 찾을 시간이 있습니다
we can still try and find your husband
before the 4:00 deadline.
두바쿠가 분명히
안 된다고 했잖나
Dubaku has specifically forbidden that.
그리고 자네 말대로라면
법 집행 기관들도 믿을 수가 없고
And according to you, I can't trust
any of my law enforcement agencies.
절 믿으십시오
You can trust me.
현재 워커 요원은 죽었다고 알려져 있고
전 아무런 신분이 없습니다
Right now everyone believes that Agent
Walker is dead, and I have no status at all.
저흰 공식적으로 존재하지 않으니
두바쿠의 첩자들도 쫓지 못할 겁니다
Which means that Dubaku's spies cannot
track us because officially we don't exist.
자넨 현직 정부 요원이 아니고
상원에선 변절자 취급을 하는데
You resigned from government service,
and the Senate regards you
as having been a renegade agent.
자네의 충성심이
어느 편인지 어떻게 알지?
How am I supposed to know
where your loyalties really lie?
외람된 말씀이지만
주변에 물어보십시오
With all due respect,
Madam President, ask around.
짧은 시간 동안
뭘 할 수 있겠나?
What could you even do
on such short notice?
장담은 못 드리지만 부군을 구하기 위해
모든 노력을 다하겠습니다
I couldn't make you any promises,
but we will do everything possible
to save your husband.
일단 두바쿠의 요구를 따르셔서
시간을 좀 벌어주십시오
Right now, we need you to go
along with Dubaku's demands.
Help buy us some time.
대통령님
선택의 여지가 없습니다
Madam President,
you don't have another choice.
알았네
All right.
그리하지
남편을 꼭 찾아주게
Find him, please?
네, 대통령님
Yes, ma'am.
보안 회선이 필요합니다
We're going to need a secure hard line.
필요하면 이 방을 쓰고
You may use this room if you need to.
준비되면 지하 통로까지
안내해 주겠네
I'll have you escorted back out through
the underground entrance when you're ready.
대통령님과 부군 경호원들의
신상 명세가 필요합니다
I'm going to need a copy of the President and
the First Gentleman's Secret Service details.
- 가져다 주라고 이르지
- 감사합니다
- I'll have them brought to you.
- Thank you.
게지 요원부터 시작하려면
최근 몇 시간의 통화 기록이 필요한데
Okay, we'll start off with Agent Gedge.
We need access to his phone records.
I want to know who he's been
talking to over the last few hours.
알다시피 대통령 보안팀엔
요청할 수 없어요
Obviously, we can't use any of
the President's security people.
고마워요
Thank you.
통화 기록은 일급 기밀이에요
대통령 가족의 경호원들은 더하죠
Phone logs are highly classified, especially
for agents assigned to the First Family.
클로이가 접근할 수 있을까요?
Can Chloe O'Brian get access?
이미 허가를 받은 사람이 있으면
더 빠르겠죠
It'll be faster if we can get someone
who's already got clearance.
래리 모스
Larry Moss.
규율에 벗어나는 일을
할 사람 같진 않던데요
He doesn't strike me as someone who's
willing to work outside the system.
그 말은 맞지만
내가 설득할 수 있어요
That's true, but I think I can
persuade him to do what we need.
그 사람을 정말
믿어요? / 네
- You really trust him?
- Yes.
우린 서로 잘 알아요
We know each other pretty well.
좋아요, 시간이 없으니
시도해 봐요
Fine. Try him.
We don't have much time.
모스 요원입니다
Agent Moss.
저 르네예요
Larry, it's Renee.
제가 살아있는 걸 아무에게도
말하면 안 돼요, 알았어요?
I'm alive, but you can't let anyone know.
Do you understand me?
세상에
Oh, my god.
르네, 대체.. 어디야?
괜찮아?
Renee? What... where are you?
Are you all right?
괜찮아요
I'm-I'm fine.
나중에 설명할 테니
지금은 우릴 좀 도와주세요
I'll explain later, but right now
we need your help.
우리라니?
Who's, who's "we"?
저와 잭 바우어요
Myself and Jack Bauer.
뭐?
What?
잭은 애초부터 우리 편이었는데
위장을 유지하려고 그랬던 거예요
He's on our side,
Larry, just like he said.
Everything that he did,
he did to preserve his cover.
르네, 여태까지
죽은 줄만 알았어
Renee, this whole time
I've been thinking you were dead.
- 왜 말해주지 않았지?
- FBI에 첩자가 있어요
- Why didn't you tell me?
- The Bureau is compromised.
FBI 내 누구도
이 작전을 알아선 안 돼요
Larry, just like he said, and no one
there can know about this operation.
완전히 비공식적으로
진행해야 해요
It has to stay completely off book.
무슨 작전이지?
What operation?
잭과 저는 백악관에 있는데
부군이 두바쿠에게 납치됐어요
Jack and I are at the White House.
The First Gentleman has
been kidnapped by Ike Dubaku.
그런 얘긴 들은 적이 없는데
I don't, I don't know
anything about that.
사실이에요, 대통령께서
우리한테 찾아달라고 하셨어요
It's true. The President's
asked Jack and me to find him.
이걸 아는 사람은 거의 없고
이대로 유지돼야 해요
Very few people know about this, and
that's the way that it has to stay.
4시까지 찾지 못하면
부군은 죽어요
If we don't find him by 4:00 P.M.,
he'll be killed.
래리
Larry...
어느 때보다 당신 믿음이
필요해요, 도와주세요
if you've ever trusted me, trust me now,
please, and help me.
어떻게 하면 될까?
What do you want me to do?
브라이언 게지라는 부군의 경호원이
연관된 것 같은데 죽었어요
Looks like the First Gentleman's Secret
Service agent was involved in all of this,
Brian Gedge, he's dead.
You need to check his phone logs
그자의 통화 기록에서 최근에
연락한 사람들에 대해 알아봐줘요
and get all the information you can about
who he's been in contact with recently.
협박당하는 게 아니고
진짜라는 걸 보여줘
I need to see you to make sure
this is real, that you're not under duress.
그럴 시간이 없어요
No, there's no time for that.
방법은 하나야
도움이 필요하면 날 만나
That's not negotiable.
You want my help, we meet.
의사당 앞 인공 호수로
최대한 빨리 와
The Capitol Reflecting Pool,
as soon as you can get there.
알았어요
Okay, fine.
도와줄 것 같은데
직접 만나야 해요
He'll help us, I think,
but we need to go.
테일러 대통령은 테러 위협이
사라졌음을 강조하며
President Taylor emphasized
the terrorists are no longer a threat
침공이 시작될 거라고 말했습니다
and says the invasion will begin.
또한 울레 마토보 전 수상이 복권되어
새 민주 정부를 수립할 거라고 밝혔습니다
She also says former Prime Minister
Ule Matobo will be reinstated
to work towards building
a new democratic government.
- 이해가 안 돼
- 뭐가요?
- I don't get it.
- What?
대통령은 CIP 장치와 마토보를
찾은 것처럼 말하는데
The President's talking as if the CIP device
and Matobo have been recovered,
어떻게 우리 모르게
그런 일이 일어날 수 있지?
but how could that have happened
without us knowing about it?
다른 기관에서 찾고도
아직 통보하지 않았나 보죠
Well, it just means whatever agency's
responsible hasn't let us know.
다른 기관이라니? 우리만
따로 노는 거 맘에 안 들어
What other agency? We're being kept
out of the loop, and I don't like it.
그럼 이따 보는 거예요?
So am I seeing you later?
모르겠어
확인할 일이 좀 있어서
I don't know. I've got
some things to figure out.
무슨 뜻이에요?
What does that mean?
집에 갈 때도 있어야지
집사람 못 본 지도 일주일 됐어
It means I have to get home at some point.
I haven't seen Christina in a week.
알았어요
All right.
션, 괜찮아요?
Sean, are you all right?
괜찮아
I'm fine.
- 좀 달라 보여서요
- 일이나 해야겠어
I'm sensing a little distance.
I just have to get back to work.
잠깐만
Excuse me.
꼭 그렇게 티를 내야겠어?
Could you be a little less obvious,
do you think?
- 무슨 소리야?
- 무슨 소리냐니
- What are you talking about?
- Give me a break.
아예 '우리 같이 자는 사이'라고
써 붙이고 다녀라
Just hold up a sign that says,
"Hey, world, we're sleeping together."
너 바보야?
Are you stupid?
바보 같고 잘못된
일인 거 알아, 끝낼 거야
I know it's stupid and wrong,
and I'm going to end it.
부장님이 알아채기 전에
빨리 끝내는 게 좋을 거야
Yeah, you'd better, fast,
before Larry notices.
- 부장님은 어딨지?
- 몰라
- Where is Larry?
- I don't know.
중요한 건 그게 아니고
부장님이 알면
That's not the point.
The point is, if he finds out about this,
넌 쥐도 새도 모르게
알래스카에 배치될 거야
he's going to transfer your ass to
Juneau so fast, your head will spin.
래리
Larry.
맙소사
Oh, my god.
다신 못 보는 줄 알았어
I thought I'd never see you again.
게지 요원의 통화 기록은
조사해 봤어요?
Were you able to access
Agent Gedge's phone records?
그래요
Yeah.
에드워드 보슬러라는 요원과
지난 3시간 동안 수차례 통화했더군
Yeah, over the last three hours,
Gedge spoke repeatedly to another
Secret Service agent named Edward Vossler.
보슬러의 개인 기록을
조사해 봤는데
I checked out Vossler's
personnel records.
경호 요원이 되기 전에
특수 부대에 있었고
Before he was a Secret Service agent,
he was special forces,
2년 동안 상갈라에서 복무했어
and for two years, served in Sangala.
보슬러와 두바쿠가
한패라고 볼 수 있겠네요
So we can assume Vossler's
working for Dubaku.
보슬러의 기록을
가져왔어요? / 그래
Did you bring any of his files
with you? / Yeah.
보슬러에게 가족이 있나요?
Does Vossler have a family?
- 그건 알아서 뭐 하게요?
- 가족이 있어요?
- Why do you need to know that?
- Does he have a family?
변호사 보조원과 결혼한 지 5년 됐고
11개월 된 아들이 있어요
He's been married for
five years to a paralegal.
They have an
11-month-old baby boy.
부인은 아이 때문에
직장을 그만뒀고요
She left her job to
stay home with the kid.
좋아요, 일을 나눕시다
그쪽은 보슬러 추적을 돕고
Okay, we're going to need to split up.
I need you to help me track Vossler.
당신은 그자의 집에 가서
가족이 있는지 봐요
I need you to go to his home
and hope his family is there.
보슬러는 특수 부대원이었으니
시간 내에 굴복시킬 수 없어요
Vossler was special forces.
There's no way we're going to break him
in the time that we've got.
협조를 받아내려면 부인과 아이를
해칠 것처럼 행동해야 해요
The only way to get him to cooperate
is to make him think we're going to hurt his family,
his wife and his kid.
안 돼, 절대 안 돼
르네?
No, absolutely not. Renee?
그건 선을 넘는 거예요, 잭
That's stepping over the line, Jack.
당신도 태너를 심문하면서
선을 넘었잖아요
You stepped over the line
the second you interrogated Tanner.
태너는 살인자고
Tanner's a murderer.
보슬러의 부인은 무고해요
아이는 말할 것도 없고요
As far as we know, Vossler's wife is
completely innocent, let alone a small child.
언제까지 모두가 우리 규칙을
따른다고 생각할 건가요?
When are you people going to stop thinking
everyone else is following your rules?
현실은 달라요!
They're not!
45분 내로 두바쿠를 찾지 못하면
헨리 테일러는 죽어요
Dubaku is going to kill Henry Taylor within
the next 45 minutes unless we find him.
두 가지 선택이 있어요
You've got one of two choices:
구출에 필요한 일을 양심 때문에
못 하겠다고 대통령께 전화하든지
Now you can either phone the President
and explain to her
that your conscience won't allow you
to do what is necessary to save him,
아니면 그냥 필요한 일을 하든지
or you can simply do what is necessary.
선택해요!
Pick one!
- 르네..
- 됐어요
- Renee?
- Larry!
르네?
Renee?
차를 가져갈 테니까, 휴대전화와
경호국 배치도로 보슬러를 추적해요
I'm going to need your vehicle. Start
tracking Vossler through his cell phone.
Utilize his Secret Service
deployment grid.
당신 자신을 봐요
Look at yourself.
필요하다고 생각되는 일을 하면서
모든 걸 잃었잖아요
You've lost everyone and everything you ever
had by doing what you think is necessary.
르네도 당신처럼 되게
놔두지 않을 거예요
I won't let you do it to her, Bauer.
Renee will not end up like you.
열쇠 줄 건가요, 말 건가요?
Are you going to give me
your keys or not?
잭.. 잭!
Jack. Jack!
규칙을 따르지 않는다면
저들과 다를 게 뭡니까?
The rules are what make us better.
오늘은 어쩔 수 없어요
Not today.
테일러의 출혈을 늦췄지만
완전히 멈출 순 없습니다
I slowed down Taylor's bleeding,
but I can't get it to stop completely.
지혈대는 최대한 꽉
묶었나? / 네
Tourniquet is as tight
as possible? / Yes.
미칼리한테 화염기가 있으니까
상처를 지져
Then cauterize the wound.
Mikali has a blowtorch.
- 쇼크 상태가 될 수도 있습니다
- 입에다 뭘 물리기나 해
- You risk Taylor going into shock.
- Just put something in his mouth.
통증 때문에
혀를 깨물면 안 되니까
I don't want him biting his tongue off
with the pain.
집에서 뭐 해?
일하러 간 줄 알았는데
Hey, what are you doing at home, huh?
I thought you'd be at work.
그랬는데 로자 언니가 식당에 전화해서
푸념을 늘어놔서 말이지
I was. Rosa called me at the diner.
She was having one of her episodes.
당신 언니 잘 알잖아
당신을 이용하는 거라고
You know your sister.
She's just manipulating you.
전화할 때마다 갈 필요는 없어
You don't have to go to
her every time she calls.
언니한텐 내가 전부야
좋게 봐줘
I'm all she has, Samuel. Be kind.
당신이 내 몫까지
착하니까 괜찮아
You know, you're kind
enough for both of us.
오늘 저녁 먹으러 올 수 있는지
확인하려고 전화했어
I just wanted to make sure that
you were still coming to dinner tonight.
어, 정말 미안한데 안 되겠어
Um, look, I'm really sorry, but I can't.
확인할 적하 목록이 산더미야
I'm looking at a stack
of shipping manifests.
안 돼! 다른 방법은 없어?
늦게 와도 괜찮아
Oh, no!
Isn't there some way?
We could do it as late as you want.
나도 그랬으면 좋겠는데
미안해, 마리카
I really wish I could.
I'm sorry, Marika.
다음에 더 잘할게, 알았지?
Uh, listen, baby,
I'll make it up to you, okay?
그래, 혹시 맘 바뀔지도 모르니까
당신 것도 준비해 놓을게
Okay. Well, I'm going to make extra
just in case you change your mind.
당신은 나한테 과분해
You're too good to me.
맞아
You're right.
식당에 다시 가볼게, 언니
괜찮지?
I have to get back to the diner, Rosa.
Are you going to be okay?
누구 전화야?
Who was that on the phone?
- 그 사람이지?
- 이제 그만 좀 해
- It was him, wasn't it?
- All right, stop.
새뮤얼을 안 좋게 보는 거 알지만
난 그 사람 사랑해
I know you don't approve of Samuel,
but I love him.
사랑한다고? 왜?
You love him? Why?
그 사람 돈 때문에?
우리 집세를 내줘서?
Because he spends money on you?
Because he pays our rent?
서로 안 지 4개월밖에 안 됐잖아
You've only known him four months.
그게 뭐 어때서?
What difference does that make?
넌 그 사람에 대해 잘 몰라
You don't know anything about him.
무역업자가 아닐 수도 있잖아
불법 체류자면 어쩔 거야?
What if he's not the
importer he says he is?
Or that he's in this country illegally?
또 시작이네
Not this again.
널 보호하려는 거야, 마리카
I'm just trying to protect you, Marika.
- 보호해 줄 필요 없어
- 아니, 필요해
- I don't need your protection.
- Yes, you do.
그 사람은..
This man isn't...
그 사람은 뭐?
Isn't what?
아니야, 아무것도
Nothing. Forget it.
미안, 이럴 시간 없어
교대 끝내고 올게
I'm sorry, I don't have time for this.
I'll be home after my shift.
함대를 철수해서 첫 번째
요구에 응하는 척한 다음
We can appear to comply with the first part
of Dubaku's demand by pulling the fleet back.
원거리 해상에서
공격하면 됩니다
Then we simply launch the
invasion from farther out at sea.
두 번째 요구는 좀 더 복잡합니다
Now, the second part of his
demand is more complicated.
마토보를 정말 넘길 생각이면
지금쯤 차에 태워야 합니다
If we were really turning Matobo over, we'd
be putting him in a car right about now.
그건 안 돼요
마토보는 지켜야 해요
That's out of the question.
We need him safe.
동의합니다
Agreed.
닮은 사람을 태워 보내고
But we can send a car with a look-alike.
잘 통제하면 마지막 순간까지
두바쿠를 속일 수 있습니다
If we handle it right, Dubaku won't be
aware of the deception until the last minute.
그때쯤이면 아마도
부군을 찾을 수 있을 겁니다
By then, hopefully,
we'll have found Henry.
대통령님, 허가하시겠습니까?
Madam President, do we have
your authorization to proceed?
그래요
Yes.
바우어입니다
Bauer.
보슬러를 찾았어요
Okay, I've got Vossler.
베세즈다 근처 순환로에서
남쪽을 향하고, 11킬로 거리예요
He's on the beltway near Bethesda,
moving south, about seven miles from you.
알았어요, 갈게요
목적지가 어디죠?
Copy that. I'm on my way.
Where's he headed?
경호국 기록에 따르면
4시에 교대해서
According to the Secret Service log,
his shift starts at 4:00 P.M.
앤드류스 공군 기지로
외국 고위 관료를 마중 나가요
He's meeting a foreign
dignitary's plane at Andrews.
잭, 잘 알겠지만
일단 그쪽 정문을 통과하면
Jack, I don't have to tell you,
once he's through that gate and onto that base,
놈을 잡을 수 없을 거예요
you're not going to be able to touch him.
정문으로 가려면 337번 도로로
되돌아가야 할 테니까
Okay, he's going to have to double back on the
337 if he wants to get through that main gate.
코네티컷 도로를 타면
따라잡을 수 있어요
I should be able to make up
time by taking Connecticut.
계속 지켜봐요
Just keep sight of him.
르네 소식은요?
보슬러 집에 도착했는지 알아요?
Have you heard from Renee?
Do we know if she's arrived
at Vossler's house yet?
아니요, 하지만
문제가 생기면 연락하겠죠
No, but she knows how to get in
touch with us if she's in trouble.
가요
Coming.
무슨 일이시죠?
Can I help you?
- 누구세요?
- 닥쳐
- Who are you?
- Shut up.
시키는 대로만 하면
목숨은 건질 수 있어
Do what I tell you, and there's
a chance you'll live through this.
- 움직이지 마!
- 애가 겁먹었어요
- Don't move!
- He's scared.
가만 있지 않으면
바로 쏘겠어
Stay where you are, or
I will shoot you where you stand.
아이를 달래려고 한다고
죽일 건가요? / 앉아
You're going to kill me for
trying to comfort my baby?
Sit down.
도대체 뭐 하는 사람인데
우리한테 이래요?
What kind of a person are you?
Doing this to us.
남편한테 물어봐
You should ask your husband that.
무슨 소리죠?
What are you talking about?
에드워드는 좋은 사람이에요
Edward is a good man.
생각보다 그 사람을
잘 모르는 것 같군
Maybe you don't know him quite
as well as you think you do.
애 앞에서 총을 겨누는
사람은 아니에요 / 닥쳐!
I know he would never point a gun
near a child. / Shut up!
손목에 수갑 채워
Put the cuff around your wrist.
- 이러지 마요
- 당장!
- Don't do this.
- Now!
지금은 어디 있죠?
Okay, where is he now?
방금 순환로를 빠져나와서
신호 때문에 멈췄어요
He just got off the beltway.
He stopped in traffic.
알렌포드 교차로로 가는 중이니까
30초면 도착해요
Okay, I'm coming up on
the intersection of Allenford and Auth.
I should be there in 30 seconds.
놈이 움직이면 알려줘요
Just let me know if he moves.
- 놈이 움직여요
- 젠장! 다음 도로는 어디죠?
He's moving. / Damn it!
What's the next street north?
백스터 도로요
잭, 거긴 일방통행이에요
Baxter drive.
But, Jack, it's a one-way street.
알았어요
Copy that.
알렌포드에서 신호를 받았어요
He made the light at Allenford.
지금 백스터 도로예요
I'm on Baxter.
15초 거리예요, 잭
He's 15 seconds away, Jack.
10초
Ten seconds.
5초
Five seconds.
찾았어요
I got him.
손들어! 당장!
Let me see your hands!
Now!
차에서 내려!
Get out of the car.
Get out of the car!
가, 어서!
Move. Move!
헨리 테일러는 어디 있지?
Where is he?
Where is Henry Taylor?
무슨 소리 하는 겁니까?
I don't know what you're talking about.
어디 있어?
Where is he?
좋아, 네 방식대로 하지
Fine, we'll do this your way.
네
Yes.
보슬러를 잡았어요
부인은 찾았나요?
I've got Vossler. You got his wife?
아이도 있어요
And his child.
- 준비됐어요?
- 네
- You ready?
- Yes.
스피커폰으로 바꿔요
Put your phone on speaker.
부인과 얘기해
Talk to your wife.
- 이 자식..
- 부인과 얘기하라고!
- You son of a bitch...
- Talk to your wife!
캐롤, 괜찮아?
Carol, are you all right?
총을 든 여자가
날 죽인다고 위협하고 있어
There's a woman with a gun.
She's threatening to kill me.
코너는 왜 울어?
Why is Conner crying?
에드워드, 무슨 일이야?
이 사람들은 누구야?
Oh, my god, Edward. What's happening?
Who are these people?
시간이 없어
You are running out of time.
이러고 싶지 않았는데
I didn't want to have to do this.
- 안 돼, 제발..
- 왜 그래?
- No, you wouldn't...
- What's happening?
몰라, 코너에게 갔어
I don't know. She's got Conner.
안 돼, 코너한테 뭔가 하려고 해!
Oh, my god, she's doing
something to Conner!
아이를 놔줘요!
Let go of my baby!
아기일 뿐이잖아요! 제발!
He's just a baby! Please!
대체 무슨 짓이지?
What the hell are you doing?
네가 멈출 수 있어
어디 있는지만 말해
You can stop this.
Just tell me where he is.
제발, 에드워드
아는 대로 얘기해!
For god's sake, Edward,
tell them what they want to know!
젠장!
알았어, 말할게!
Damn it! All right, all right,
I'll tell you!
물러서요, 다시 연락할게요
Stand down. I'll get back to you.
아이는 괜찮아요
Your baby's fine.
당신은 사람도 아니야!
You're a monster!
어디 있어?
Where is he?
말하지 않으면 가족 상황이
더 나빠질 수도 있어, 어디 있어?
You tell me now, or the situation for your
family goes from bad to worse. Where is he?
가족을 죽이지 않을 걸
어떻게 알지?
How do I know you're just
not going to kill them anyway?
모르지
You don't.
좋아
Fine.
알링턴 가 12451번지
가게 지하실에 있어
There's a greengrocer,
12451 Arlington Avenue.
They're holding him in the basement.
접근 방법은?
Access.
뒤쪽에 계단이 있는데
항상 잠겨 있어
There's a staircasein the back,
but it's always locked.
- 두바쿠도 있나?
- 아깐 있었어
- Is Dubaku with him?
- He was.
- 무장 인원은 몇 명이지?
- 최소 4명
- How many guns are guarding him?
- At least four.
꺼져!
Get out of here!
차에서 떨어져!
Get away from the car!
어서 물러나!
Walk away! Now!
젠장
Damn it.
멈춰!
차에서 내려, 어서!
Stop! Get out of the car now!
Move! Move!
마토보를 넘길 것처럼 하면서
최대한 시간을 끄는 게 목표입니다
The goal is to make it look like we're going to hand
Matobo over for as long as is reasonably possible.
접선 지점에 가면
두바쿠 부하들과 거리를 유지하고
When you get to the rendezvous point,
keep your distance from Dubaku's men.
뒷좌석에 있는 걸 보여주되
차에서 내리진 마요
Let them see you in the backseat,
but do not get out of the car.
안전 거리 이상으로
다가오게 하면 안 됩니다
Don't let them get any closer
than you feel comfortable with.
위험하다고 생각되면
당장 빠져나와요
As soon as you start to feel that
the risk is unacceptable, get the hell out.
대통령께서 직접 내리신
명령입니다, 알았어요?
That's straight from
the President. Clear?
알겠습니다
Clear.
행운을 빕니다
Good luck.
잭 / 헨리 테일러가
있는 곳을 알아냈어요
Jack? / I got an address
for Henry Taylor.
알링턴 가 12451번지 가게의
지하실에 잡혀 있어요
12451 Arlington Avenue. It's a storefront.
He's being held in the basement.
나보다 먼저 도착하면
그대로 있어요
If you get there before I do,
I want you to stand down.
무장 인원이 4명 이상이에요
Dubaku's got at least four gunmen there.
알았어요
All right.
가면서 빌한테 보고할 테니
당신은 래리한테 연락해요
Meanwhile, I'm going to call Bill, pull him up to speed.
I want you to do the same thing with Larry.
- 보슬러는 어떻게 됐어요?
- 죽었어요
- And what about Vossler?
- He's dead.
날 공격해서
어쩔 수 없었어요
He attacked me.
I didn't have a choice.
괜찮아요?
Are you okay?
아니요, 안 괜찮아요
No, I don't think I am.
무슨 소리예요?
문제 있어요?
What do you mean?
What's wrong?
워커 요원, 듣고 있어요?
Agent Walker, are you still there?
더는..
I'm not...
내 말 들어요
Listen to me.
당신이 아니었으면
여기까지 오지 못했을 거예요
We could not have gotten this far
if it wasn't for you. Okay?
감당하기 힘든 일이었다 해도
당신을 탓할 사람은 없어요
No one would blame you if this was
just too much for you to handle.
일단 거기서 나와요
Maybe you should get out.
그래야겠네요
Maybe I will.
그래요
Yeah.
내일 봐요
Tomorrow.
매스든 요원과 가고 있습니다
Agent Masden and I are on our way.
위성으로 지켜보고 있을 테니
발전소에 도착하면 연락하게 / 네
We'll be tracking you via satellite.
Check in with me when you're
approaching the power plant.
Yes, sir.
이걸로 얼마나 시간을
벌 수 있을까요?
How much time do you
think this will buy us?
마토보가 아니란 걸 알 때까지
10분이나 15분 정도일 겁니다
Until Dubaku realizes
Matobo's not in the limo.
Ten minutes, maybe 15.
주어진 시간보다
15분 더 연장되는군요
That's 15 minutes more than we had.
대통령님, 방금 잭 바우어에게
연락이 왔는데
Madam President, I just got off
the phone with Jack Bauer.
부군의 위치를 알아낸 것 같습니다
He and Agent Walker think
they have a location on your husband.
어딘가? / 알링턴 가입니다
지금 그리로 가고 있습니다
Where? / Arlington Avenue.
They're on their way now.
- 얼마나 걸릴 것 같나?
- 10분에서 15분 정도입니다
- How long will it take them?
- Ten, 15 minutes.
고맙네
Thank you.
국토안보부에서 들어온 건데
우리가 제외됐다는 말이 맞네요
This just came over from Homeland.
Like you said,
we're being kept out of the loop.
고마워
Thanks.
이거 보셨어요?
Did you see this?
대통령 요청에 따라 국토안보부에서
경보 수준을 낮추려고 해요
Homeland's preparing to lower
the threat level at the President's request.
- 그래, 나도 봤네
- 이상하지 않아요?
- Yeah, I saw the flash.
- Don't you think that's odd,
CIP 장치를 회수한 것에 대해
우리만 모르는 게 말이에요
considering we don't know anything
about the CIP device being recovered?
국토안보부에 연락해보지
Yeah. I'll talk to Homeland.
제 말은.. 우리 모르게
뭔가 진행되고 있다는 생각이 들어요
All I'm saying is... I get the feeling like
there's something going on behind our back here.
말했잖아, 알아본다고
Like I said, I'll talk to them.
- 잠시만
- 네
- Excuse me.
- Yeah, sure.
어디야? / 헨리 테일러가
잡혀 있는 곳으로 가고 있어요
Where are you?
On my way to where we think
Henry Taylor's being held.
보슬러의 입을 열었군
So you got Vossler to talk.
부군을 구출할
유일한 기회가 생겼죠
It gave us our only chance to
rescue the President's husband.
주소는?
기동대를 파견할게
What's the address?
I'll send a SWAT team to meet you.
FBI 내부 첩자 때문에
안 되는 거 알잖아요
You know you can't do that.
The Bureau's compromised.
구출 작전이 무산될 거예요
It will jeopardize any attempt
that we make.
당신이 해줄 일은 따로 있어요
But there is something else
I need you to do.
그게 뭔데?
Okay, what's that?
잭과 작전을 진행하는 동안
사건 하나를 덮어주세요
Keep an incident quiet until what
Jack and I are doing goes down.
무슨 사건?
What incident?
보슬러가 죽었어요
Vossler's dead.
잭이 리긴 18번가 호텔에서
죽였는데 정당방위였어요
Jack killed him at the hotel on
18th and Riggin. It was self-defense.
- 잭이 그렇게 말하던가?
- 래리
- Is that what he told you?
- Larry...
젠장, 잭과 무슨 짓을
하고 있는 거야?
Damn it, Renee, what the hell
are you doing with this guy?
용의자를 잡아들여야지
죽이면 어떡해
We're supposed to bring
suspects in, not murder them.
제발.. 첩자가 밝혀지기 전까진
FBI 외부에서 처리해주세요
Larry, please...
and until we know
who Dubaku's source is there,
you've got to handle this outside
of the Bureau, okay?
경찰에 믿을 만한 사람이 있으니까
보슬러 문제를 처리하라고 할게
There's a guy at D.C. Metro
I know I can trust.
I'll have him deal with Vossler.
고마워요
Thank you, Larry.
알았어요, 그렇게 보고하죠
I understand. I will let him know.
정보원에 따르면, 마토보를 태운
차량이 백악관을 출발했답니다
According to our sources, a vehicle
containing Matobo just left the White House.
좋아
미군의 상태는?
Good. What is the state of
the American invasion forces?
함대가 상갈라 영해를 벗어나
경선 23도로 향하고 있습니다 / 좋아
The fleet is withdrawing from Sangalan
territorial waters,
and has set steam for
the 23rd meridian. / Excellent.
- 여보세요
- 로자예요
- Hello.
- It's Rosa.
로자, 마리카는 지금 여기 없는데
Rosa, if you're looking for Marika,
she's not with me.
당신한테 할 말이 있어요, 새뮤얼
I'm looking for you, Samuel.
진짜 이름은 뭔지 모르겠지만
Or whatever your real name is.
무슨 소리예요?
What are you talking about?
동생은 순진할지 몰라도
난 아니에요
My sister may be naive, but I'm not.
이민국의 아는 사람한테
알아봤는데
I checked with someone I know
at Immigration Services,
상갈라에서 이주한 새뮤얼 아보아란
사람은 지난 15년간 없었다는군요
and no one named Samuel Aboa emigrated from
Sangala in the last year, or in the last 15 years.
뭔가 실수가 있었겠죠
Well, they've obviously made a mistake.
실수는 당신이 하고 있어요
You're making a mistake.
당신 정체가 뭔지 모르고
상관도 안 해요
Now I don't know who you really are,
and I don't care.
내 동생 인생을 건드리지만 마요
I just want you out of my sister's life.
- 마리카도 이 사실을 알아요?
- 아직 몰라요
- Does Marika know about this?
- No, not yet.
앞으로도 그럴 거고요
And I'm willing to keep it that way.
- 그럼 신고하지 않았단 말이죠?
- 네, 마리카가 아는 걸 원치 않아요
So you've not reported me
to anyone? / No.
I don't want Marika to
know anything about this.
- 원하는 게 뭐예요?
- 그 애와 헤어져요
- What do you want?
- Break up with her,
그럼 비밀은 지킬게요
and this stays between us.
오늘 밤에 헤어지면
아무 문제 없을 거예요
You just end it tonight,
and we won't have a problem.
작은 문제가 생겨서 가봐야 하니까
마토보를 데려오면 연락해
I have to take care of a little problem.
Call me when we have Matobo.
네 / 마토보를 가장한 차량이
발전소에 곧 도착하네
Yeah.
The vehicle that's supposed to be delivering
Matobo is arriving at the power plant.
더 늦어지면 두바쿠가
의심할 텐데 그쪽은 어떤가?
If we delay any longer, Dubaku is going
to get suspicious. What's your status?
거의 다 왔어요
얼마나 시간을 벌 수 있죠?
I'm almost there.
How much time can you buy us?
모르겠네, 잭
I don't know, Jack.
알았어요
도착하는 대로 들어갈게요
Okay, Agent Walker and I will
move in as soon as I get there.
- 또 연락할게요
- 좋아, 행운을 비네
- I'll keep you posted.
- All right, good luck.
스미스 요원입니다
두바쿠 부하들이 보입니다
This is Agent Smith.
We've got a visual on Dubaku's men.
알았어요
위성으로 보고 있어요
Understood. We have it on satellite.
마토보를 데려와
Bring him to us.
차에서 내리라고 하더니
한 명이 전화를 하고 있습니다
They've ordered us
to get out of the car.
Now one of them is making a call.
조금만 버텨요
Hang tight, agent.
차는 도착했는데
아무 일도 없습니다
Their car arrived, but
nothing is happening.
아무 일도 없다니?
What do you mean nothing is happening?
마토보를 데려오라고 했는데
아무도 차에서 안 내립니다
We ordered them to hand Matobo over to us,
but no one's getting out of the vehicle.
미국놈들이 우릴 속였어
차를 폭파해 / 네
The Americans have been playing us.
Destroy their vehicle.
Yes, sir.
이 정도면 됐어요
어서 빠져나오라고 해요
That's long enough.
Get them the hell out of there.
퇴각 명령이에요
어서 빠져나와요
Retreat.
Get out now.
알았어요
Roger that.
- 준비됐어요?
- 네
- You ready?
- Yes.
갑시다
Let's go.
계산대 뒤에서 나와
어서!
Get out from behind the counter.
Now! Move!
문을 열고 놈들에게
먹을 거 필요하냐고 물어봐
Okay, I want you to unlock that door.
And I want you to ask those men
what they want to eat.
허튼짓했다간 머리통을
날려버릴 거야, 알았어?
You do one thing I don't like, and I will
blow your head off, you understand me?
문 열어
Open the door.
먹을 거 필요해요?
Want anything to eat?
- 아니, 찬 맥주나 줘
- 네
- No. Some cold beers.
- Okay.
영어대본
http://sfile.ydy.com
싱크편집
윤선영(seedyun@nate.com)
한글번역
정광재(indioblu@nate.com)
번역수정
김혜정(heather81@nate.com)
네
Yes.
헨리 테일러를 죽여
Kill Henry Taylor.
- 그럼 놈들을 위협할 게 없잖아요
- 지금도 없어
Then we have nothing to
hold over their heads.
We don't have anything now.
대통령이 남편의 죽음을
감수할 생각이더군
The President was willing to let him die.
We are done here.
테일러를 죽이고
철수할 준비 해
Kill Taylor, and have your men
pack everything up.
알겠습니다
Understood.
세상에, 부군..
Oh, my god.
Sir... sir...
저희가 도와드리겠습니다
정신 차리세요
We're going to get you help.
Just stay with me.
구급차 불러요!
Get an ambulance!
자막제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
(http://club.nate.com/24)
조건부 배포 / 수정금지
배포시 자막 출처를 꼭 밝혀주세요